export const chapter = "Chapter - 8: Kolkata: The City of Joy";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "What is the main river on the east bank of which Kolkata is situated?",
        optionA: "Ganges",
        optionB: "Brahmaputra",
        optionC: "Hooghly",
        correctAnswer: "Hooghly",
      },
      {
        question: "What was the previous name of Kolkata?",
        optionA: "Mumbai",
        optionB: "Calcutta",
        optionC: "Delhi",
        correctAnswer: "Calcutta",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which British Empire period saw Kolkata as the capital of British India?",
        optionA: "1857-1947",
        optionB: "1773-1911",
        optionC: "1947-1962",
        correctAnswer: "1773-1911",
      },
      {
        question: "What is Kolkata also known as?",
        optionA: "The Garden City",
        optionB: "The City of Joy",
        optionC: "The City of Dreams",
        correctAnswer: "The City of Joy",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the main language spoken in Kolkata?",
        optionA: "English",
        optionB: "Hindi",
        optionC: "Bengali",
        correctAnswer: "Bengali",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which festival is celebrated with great joy for ten days in Kolkata?",
        optionA: "Diwali",
        optionB: "Holi",
        optionC: "Durga Puja",
        correctAnswer: "Durga Puja",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which iconic landmark of Kolkata is considered one of the longest cantilever bridges in the world?",
        optionA: "Vidyasagar Setu",
        optionB: "Howrah Bridge (Rabindra Setu)",
        optionC: "Victoria Memorial",
        correctAnswer: "Howrah Bridge (Rabindra Setu)",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the main industry in Kolkata?",
        optionA: "IT and Software",
        optionB: "Jute processing",
        optionC: "Textile manufacturing",
        correctAnswer: "Jute processing",
      },
      {
        question: "How is Kolkata connected to other parts of India?",
        optionA: "Only by airways",
        optionB: "By roadways, railways, and airways",
        optionC: "Only by railways",
        correctAnswer: "By roadways, railways, and airways",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the name of Kolkata's international airport?",
        optionA: "Rajiv Gandhi International Airport",
        optionB: "Indira Gandhi International Airport",
        optionC: "Netaji Subhash Chandra Bose International Airport",
        correctAnswer: "Netaji Subhash Chandra Bose International Airport",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "Kolkata is India's ____________ largest city and is among one of the four metropolitan cities of India.",
        optionA: "Second",
        optionB: "Third",
        optionC: "Fourth",
        correctAnswer: "Second",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Kolkata is situated on the east bank of the river ____________.",
        optionA: "Ganges",
        optionB: "Brahmaputra",
        optionC: "Hooghly",
        correctAnswer: "Hooghly",
      },
      {
        question: "It is the state capital of ____________.",
        optionA: "Uttar Pradesh",
        optionB: "West Bengal",
        optionC: "Bihar",
        correctAnswer: "West Bengal",
      },
      {
        question: "Kolkata was earlier known as ____________.",
        optionA: "Chennai",
        optionB: "Calcutta",
        optionC: "Mumbai",
        correctAnswer: "Calcutta",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Kolkata was the capital of British India from ____________ to 1911.",
        optionA: "1857",
        optionB: "1773",
        optionC: "1911",
        correctAnswer: "1773",
      },
      {
        question: "Kolkata is also nicknamed as the ____________.",
        optionA: "City of Dreams",
        optionB: "City of Joy",
        optionC: "City of Love",
        correctAnswer: "City of Joy",
      },
      {
        question:
          "People of all over the country live in Kolkata. ____________ is the main language spoken here.",
        optionA: "English",
        optionB: "Bengali",
        optionC: "Hindi",
        correctAnswer: "Bengali",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Kolkatans like to eat rice and fish. They are fond of sweets like ____________.",
        optionA: "Pizza and Burgers",
        optionB: "Rasgulla and Sandesh",
        optionC: "Ice Cream and Chocolate",
        correctAnswer: "Rasgulla and Sandesh",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Kolkata is connected to all parts of India by ____________, ____________, and ____________.",
        optionA: "Railways, Airports, and Waterways",
        optionB: "Roadways, Railways, and Airways",
        optionC: "Highways, Ferries, and Helipads",
        correctAnswer: "Roadways, Railways, and Airways",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Kolkata also has an international airport named ____________.",
        optionA: "Rajiv Gandhi International Airport",
        optionB: "Indira Gandhi International Airport",
        optionC: "Netaji Subhash Chandra Bose International Airport",
        correctAnswer: "Netaji Subhash Chandra Bose International Airport",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "The principal is responsible for teaching different subjects.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "The sports teacher's primary role is to teach sports.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "The dance teacher is responsible for teaching dance.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "The receptionist issues books to the students.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "The librarian watches the school gate.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "The peon looks after the plants at the school.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "The guard receives visitors and telephone calls.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "The bus driver brings the students to the school.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "The subject teachers teach different subjects.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "All other persons at school work under the principal's guidance.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        correctAnswer: "True",
      },
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
